<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-12-23T08:07:40+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Money Or Art</title><link href="/2022/12/23/Money-Or-Art.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Money Or Art" /><published>2022-12-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/12/23/Money-Or-Art</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/23/Money-Or-Art.html"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How Much Pain Can You Tolerate?</title><link href="/2022/12/21/How-Much-Pain-Can-You-Tolerate.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How Much Pain Can You Tolerate?" /><published>2022-12-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/12/21/How-Much-Pain-Can-You-Tolerate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/21/How-Much-Pain-Can-You-Tolerate.html"><![CDATA[<p>CHILL</p>

<p>CHILL CHILL</p>

<p>I Don’t write much.</p>

<p>Mind yaps a lot.</p>

<p>Truth kills you.</p>

<p>All selves are destined to Unite.</p>

<p>The Bible has its roots in Astrology.</p>

<p>I am still bound in shackles.</p>

<p>What is Letting Go really?</p>

<p>Do we need Books and Techniques?</p>

<p>What can I not let go of?</p>

<p>What If I did let go of wanting to be great?</p>

<p>What If I did let go of wanting to survive?</p>

<p>What If I did let go of being run by fear?</p>

<p>What If I followed my heart no matter where It may take me?</p>

<p>What If I replaced the fear of death with only Truth?</p>

<p>What if there was no difference between anything?</p>

<p>What is Fear? and why do we avoid it?</p>

<p>What is the pain hidden away in my gut?</p>

<p>How can I stop being run by Fear?</p>

<p>Is a Life without Fear possible?</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>All Fear is Fear of Oneself</p>

  <p>– Kapil Gupta, MD</p>
</blockquote>

<p>What do you do with Fear?</p>

<ul>
  <li>Uproot it (Letting Go) (Head On)</li>
  <li>Be Present and Understand where it comes from (stroll)</li>
  <li>Vibrate with a high frequency to avoid being controlled by it</li>
</ul>

<p>All three necessitate being Present with the feeling and not avoiding it in any way.</p>

<p>Where is the Heart and Mind in the Letting Go technique?</p>

<p>Maybe I should actually finish reading the damn book?</p>

<p>My Inkling is that just concentrating on feeling the emotion can amplify It and does not actually resolve it. What resolves it is a recontextualization of the feeling in the present context. So feeling the emotion, yes, but also not losing awareness of everything around it, the whole body, thoughts and the outside.</p>

<p>Or is fear and stored pain just a message from the past that is resolved by understanding the message?</p>

<p>Or is fear resolved by becoming one with it? Not trying to get rid of it?</p>

<p>To live without fear one has to let go of all fears. That seems obvious. -&gt; Let’s presume the opposite, that you <strong>can</strong> live without fear, but buried deep within there still is the fear of death. In that case, since we live in a world with threat in it, that fear will get triggered anyways.</p>

<p>But Alan Watts and the Zen are saying that ultimately, the fear comes from within. That the mind creates it. Yes, threat exists, danger exists, but we have the power to interpret it in any way we want to. And so we can fear it and act based on that emotion, or we can become present and not let circumstance cause any self-inflicted pain.</p>

<p>I used to self-inflict so much pain.</p>

<p>I blamed myself and made myself suffer because I didn’t know any other way to deal with major problems.</p>

<p>I was anxious in social situations.</p>

<p>I was anxious in most of school.</p>

<p>I had to suppress anxiousness for hours on end. Day after day. I guess that <strong>is</strong> part of the deep buried pain.</p>

<p>I guess that made it easier to tolerate fear and anxiousness in the future. I am sure it is not the optimal solution.</p>

<p>Let’s see what Letting Go Chapter about Fear says.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>The Unconscious is crude and uncivilized. Symbols of the Unconscious are just Symbols. ???</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>We hold an unconscious belief that fear keeps us alive, when in reality the opposite is true. Fear keeps us from being alive.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>What Concrete Fears do I have?</p>

<ul>
  <li>That someone will get angry at me and murder me</li>
  <li>That I will get laughed at by people</li>
  <li>That I’ll let myself down</li>
  <li>That I will get judged by my appearance</li>
  <li>That I will self-inflict more pain.</li>
  <li>That I’ll feel fear</li>
  <li>That I’ll feel pain and suffer</li>
</ul>

<blockquote>
  <p>Guilt accompanies all negative emotions and throws one out of balance and makes them weaker.</p>

  <p>Guilt is a substitute for reality and almost always has nothing to do with the truth of the situation.</p>

  <p>Disease is unlikely to exist without guilt and guilt is a denial of our inner intrinsic innocence.</p>

  <p>Guilt and self-inflicted pain are programmed in us by society. The Truth is, it is only there to keep us down.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>I am arrogant.</p>

<p>I avoid getting to the bottom of contradictions in me.</p>

<p>I avoid admitting my ignorance.</p>

<p>I fear fear.</p>

<p>I fear feeling the pain and not getting anywhere. I fear suffering unnecessarily. I haven’t become convinced of our inner innocence.</p>

<p>I predict more dark traumas lurking beneath the pain in my stomach I call the black hole.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHILL]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Am I Dependent On Others?</title><link href="/2022/12/13/Am-I-dependent-on-others.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Am I Dependent On Others?" /><published>2022-12-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/12/13/Am-I-dependent-on-others</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/13/Am-I-dependent-on-others.html"><![CDATA[<p>Of course I am.</p>

<p>How can I not be. I was born a son of slaves in a society of slaves. In a place where truth costs money, survival costs freedom, thriving necessitates lies.</p>

<p>What am I waiting for? Why am I not following my heart and going against all conventions to be sovereign.</p>

<p>Everyone and everything that’s keeping me from being sovereign must be abandoned.</p>

<p>The Luxuries of the Home must be left behind and familiar people have to be ghosted.</p>

<p>People will be upset and lonely. People will blame me for their pain. People will curse me. People may be let down. People may be disappointed.</p>

<p>People <strong>will</strong> be disappointed.</p>

<p>I have not taken responsibility for their well-being.</p>

<p>How can I let down my family?</p>

<p>Why should I let down my family?</p>

<p>What am I to do?</p>

<p>Is serving the Truth selfish?</p>

<p>What if my self is distorting the Truth?</p>

<p>My self is absolutely distorting the Truth.</p>

<p>Why am I carrying others voices in my head?</p>

<p>Which voice is the honest one?</p>

<p>Why is being honest and vulnerable so hard?</p>

<p>This kind of coughin don’t need lean.</p>

<p>Where is the wink of the universe?</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of course I am.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mental Freedom</title><link href="/2022/12/13/Mental-Freedom.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mental Freedom" /><published>2022-12-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/12/13/Mental-Freedom</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/13/Mental-Freedom.html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
  <p>When one fully realizes that most prior meaning making was socially and culturally conditioned, scientific certainty and the judgmental frame of mind break down. <strong>Moreover, Individualists can learn to consciously scrutinize their beliefs in order to test their assumptions or to relish the novel mental freedom such a maneuver opens up.</strong> A big discovery for this stage is the relativity of points of view. When people first become aware of this, they may see everything as relative and reject any prior certainties including scientific knowledge as absolute and therefore “false.” It takes experience at this stage to realize that successful living likely requires some of the earlier values. Most individuals need to make a living to survive. Sticking with a job one may not totally like and getting along with others who do not appreciate constant questioning is thus a requirement for most adults no matter how creative and postconventional one may be.</p>

  <p>– Suzanne Cook-Greuter (Ego Development: A Full-Spectrum Theory Of Vertical Growth And Meaning)</p>
</blockquote>

<p>I want to believe mental freedom isn‘t dependent on whether you’re in a jail cell or on a planet by yourself, but I think it <strong>is</strong> dependent on wether one uses all resources available to him to live and express freedom to the highest degree he understands it. Otherwise, he will forever be the victim of his own self-imposed limitations, because, I can’t imagine a person experiencing true freedom and not longing for it ever after. The feeling of true freedom is natures biggest gift.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[When one fully realizes that most prior meaning making was socially and culturally conditioned, scientific certainty and the judgmental frame of mind break down. Moreover, Individualists can learn to consciously scrutinize their beliefs in order to test their assumptions or to relish the novel mental freedom such a maneuver opens up. A big discovery for this stage is the relativity of points of view. When people first become aware of this, they may see everything as relative and reject any prior certainties including scientific knowledge as absolute and therefore “false.” It takes experience at this stage to realize that successful living likely requires some of the earlier values. Most individuals need to make a living to survive. Sticking with a job one may not totally like and getting along with others who do not appreciate constant questioning is thus a requirement for most adults no matter how creative and postconventional one may be. – Suzanne Cook-Greuter (Ego Development: A Full-Spectrum Theory Of Vertical Growth And Meaning)]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">No Limits</title><link href="/2022/12/07/No-Limits.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="No Limits" /><published>2022-12-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/12/07/No-Limits</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/07/No-Limits.html"><![CDATA[<p>There are no limits in the present.</p>

<p>It does not matter why you thought you could never do something, in the present you can do anything. In the present, you have choice. You have control. <strong>In the present you have freedom.</strong></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are no limits in the present.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mass Slavery</title><link href="/2022/12/04/Mass-Slavery.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mass Slavery" /><published>2022-12-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/12/04/Mass-Slavery</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/04/Mass-Slavery.html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
  <p><strong>Money is the most widespread belief system in the world.</strong></p>

  <p>– Mark Passio</p>
</blockquote>

<p>If money is imaginary, why do I have anxiety about not having any?</p>

<div style="padding:60% 0 0 0;position:relative;"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/128421102?h=b2c2e98b16&amp;color=ffffff&amp;byline=0&amp;portrait=0" style="position:absolute;top:0;left:0;width:100%;height:100%;" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; fullscreen; picture-in-picture"></iframe></div>
<script src="https://player.vimeo.com/api/player.js"></script>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Money is the most widespread belief system in the world. – Mark Passio]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dopamine Rat</title><link href="/2022/12/03/Dopamine-Rat.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dopamine Rat" /><published>2022-12-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/12/03/Dopamine-Rat</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/03/Dopamine-Rat.html"><![CDATA[<p>FUCK YEAH</p>

<p>I Smoked one!</p>

<p>Not One I Smoked Six.</p>

<p>Anddd…. I’m Done.</p>

<p>If truth compounds, then why does truth about smoking not compound?</p>

<p>Why is it so hard to quit?</p>

<h1 id="i-quit">I QUIT</h1>

<p>F yeah!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[FUCK YEAH]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Acid Rat</title><link href="/2022/12/02/Acid-Rat.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Acid Rat" /><published>2022-12-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/12/02/Acid-Rat</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/02/Acid-Rat.html"><![CDATA[<p>Internalized voices.</p>

<p>The Truth is always just there. There is no way to get closer to it or to understand it or do anything about it. You can either appreciate it or do anything else you want. You choose. No difference in the end. We all die.</p>

<p>F Society.</p>

<p>F Language.</p>

<p>The programming has to be dropped at a certain point.</p>

<p>At a certain point, the programming has to be dropped.</p>

<p>What if I was born in a family that lived by the Truth. Like in the Countryside growing its own food? &gt; Then I’d be an alien not understanding people.</p>

<p>You have to grow out of society. Even though it’s despicable with making you believe lies, you have to learn its ropes if you want to understand it. If you want to use it to your advantage, say, sell a product, you have to have learned it.</p>

<p>You get paid for providing VALUE.</p>

<p>You can provide VALUE to 1 Person/Entity -&gt; Job</p>

<p>You can provide VALUE to a type of Person (avatar) (group) -&gt; Niche Business</p>

<p><u>Eventually</u> You provide VALUE to everybody because your contribution <em>dissipates</em>.</p>

<h3 id="money"><u>Money</u></h3>

<p>F TradFi. We doing EthFi where you can actually see money.</p>

<p>What about Monero and money privacy?</p>

<p>You know, money could use a nice reimagigning.</p>

<p>What is Money, Finance and Economics?</p>

<p>How does traditional economics work? How is crypto different?</p>

<p>How long do I need to read Taleb’s Incerto? 1 Month? Maybe 37 Days?</p>

<p>Is being Great enough, or do you have to be able to explain the how..? &gt; Fuck the explaining (voice), be great, people will appreciate you. Kanye can’t explain himself.. But he, in contrast to you, has a grind to go back to. And eventually the grind sharpens the blade sharper than any sperm and egg could.</p>

<p>NO PERSCRIPTIONS IS THE ONLY PERSCRIPTION WHICH HAS TO BE NOED EVENTUALLY ASWELL..</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internalized voices.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A lot happened, yet I’m still not done</title><link href="/2022/12/01/A-lot-happened-yet-I'm-still-not-done.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A lot happened, yet I’m still not done" /><published>2022-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/12/01/A-lot-happened-yet-I'm-still-not-done</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/01/A-lot-happened-yet-I'm-still-not-done.html"><![CDATA[<p>Truth is yet to be found.</p>

<p>No pursuit other than that of Truth comes close to being real and making me feel alive!</p>

<p>With Truth, you don’t have to make a decision about what to do or think about. You just devote yourself to the Truth in the present and you can be sure that it will take you to the correct destination.</p>

<p>Fukk Sleep. I’m avoiding the Truth when sleeping all day. And Carbs make me sleepy fuck.</p>

<ol>
  <li>
    <p>The entire Universe is within me and accessible by changing my frequency as to resonate with it and understand it completely.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Sincerity is honesty about not understanding. It causes the questioning of one’s set in stone assumptions. Insencere questions don’t solve problems.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <blockquote>
      <p>The Solution to a Problem lies squarely deep in Understanding the problem — Kapil Gupta, MD</p>

      <p>Also listen to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sBtuqpNZwio" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Master Kapil Gupta speaking about solutions to problems</a>.</p>
    </blockquote>
  </li>
</ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Truth is yet to be found.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Love Strong Desire</title><link href="/2022/11/30/Love-Strong-Desire.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Love Strong Desire" /><published>2022-11-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/11/30/Love-Strong-Desire</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/11/30/Love-Strong-Desire.html"><![CDATA[<p>What comes next is really important.</p>

<p>​	Might be the most important move yet.</p>

<p>If Mind is about making destinctions.</p>

<p>Mind is about approaching creation in ever finer detail. Exactly like a mandlebrot zoom.</p>

<p><img src="../assets/images/image-20221130220020632.png" alt="image-20221130220020632" /></p>

<p>If mind is all around, then what’s the point of choosing it?</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p>At least I’m making progress. At least I’m moving.</p>

<p>I’m forgetting myself and then it’s fun to find myself again.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What comes next is really important.]]></summary></entry></feed>